[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Right-handed people live longer than left-handed people.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1889, this French car brand produced its first automobile, a three-wheeled car powered by steam and designed by Leon Serpollet.", "correct_answer": "Peugeot", "incorrect_answers": ["Renault", "Bugatti", "Citroen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do farmers raise nutrias for?", "correct_answer": "Their fur is very valuable.", "incorrect_answers": ["Their huge teeth can be sold as jewelry.", "They can use their oil for shampoos and lotions.", "Their milk is very nutritious."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American physicist was the youngest group leader of the Manhattan Project, a joint effort by the US and their WW II allies to develop the first nuclear weapons.", "correct_answer": "Robert R. Wilson", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry DeWolf Smyth", "Edward Teller", "Ernest O. Lawrence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the 1949 mystery movie directed by Carol Reed and featuring Orson Welles.", "correct_answer": "The Third Man", "incorrect_answers": ["The First Man", "The Fourth Man", "The Second Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is present on the national flag of Norway?", "correct_answer": "Cross", "incorrect_answers": ["Star", "Sun", "Mountain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What present does Kelly give to Chuck upon his departure in the Cast Away movie?", "correct_answer": "Timepiece", "incorrect_answers": ["Pen", "Her diary", "Flashlight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which casino game gives you the best chance of winning? (We assume that no cheating is involved.)", "correct_answer": "Blackjack", "incorrect_answers": ["Keno", "Slot machines", "Craps"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Canadian city is the site of the haunted Carleton County Jail, said to be the home of the ghost of Patrick Whelen, hanged for the murder of Thomas DArcy McGee?", "correct_answer": "Ottawa, Ontario", "incorrect_answers": ["Montreal, Quebec", "Barkerville, British Columbia", "Bad Hills, Saskatchewan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Louis Winthorpes fianc\u00e9e in the movie Trading Places?", "correct_answer": "Penelope", "incorrect_answers": ["Amber", "Fifi", "Clara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nigel Bruce portrayed Dr. Watson in what 1939 film?", "correct_answer": "The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes", "incorrect_answers": ["The Adventures of Philip Marlowe", "The Adventures of Dick Tracy", "The Adventures of Sam Spade"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which blood constituent is involved in the formation of blood clots but has a shelf-life of only 5 days?", "correct_answer": "platelets", "incorrect_answers": ["red blood cells", "plasma", "white blood cells"]}]